Kareem Hamada

Al Bahr al Ahmar, Egypt



kareemhamada219@gmail.com



01090802802



linkedin.com/in/kareem-hamada-139574217

Summary

I am a backend developer with experience in building websites and web applications. I specialize in Python and have professional experience working with Django. I also have experience working with Javascript, HTML, CSS, Sass, bootstrap, and fewer experiences with React.

Experience



Trainee at Information Technology Institute (ITI)

Information Technology Institute (ITI)

Aug 2021 - Sep 2021 (2 months)

- Advanced my experience in front-end web development.
- Built websites with JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Sass, and bootstrap.
- Built a responsive medical website as a graduation project.

Trainee at Egyptian Space Agency

EgSA-Egyptian Space Agency

Jul 2021 - Sep 2021 (3 months)

Project Name: The satellites swarm system.

Description of project: The satellites swarm system (SSS) is a system that consists of a network of satellites orbiting in space that communicate with each other in space through antennas mounted on the satellite and are controlled by a group of ground stations.

It was my first time to work with embedded systems like arduino and gain more experience.

My role in the team: - I was responsible for some functions of the project, built a simple UI, and integrating code.

Education



Faculty of Computer and Information Suez University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 2018 - 2022

Licenses & Certifications



Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python) - Coursera

TKM7UT45EVSV



Python Data Structures - Coursera

X7PP7BSEUXFF

- Using Databases with Python Coursera
 6N8TB2TUA3YK
- Capstone: Retrieving, Processing, and Visualizing Data with Python Coursera
 NFQW4QDU6J8A
- Using Python to Access Web Data Coursera
 UWKCY9K76JEN
- Python for Everybody Specialization Coursera 2R8EU5LULLBN
- Getting started as a freelancer (Upwork) Information Technology Institute (ITI) ilp3GBLLcZ
- Freelancing Basics Information Technology Institute (ITI)

 0mjY1yQJar
- Web development challenger track Udacity LGAYJ5SG
- React JS Information Technology Institute (ITI)

 CYTpDQXrcy

Skills

Web Development • Python (Programming Language) • JavaScript • Django • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • React.js • SQL • MySQL • Problem Solving